solidsolutions.co.uk 2017-09-28

# Privacy Policy

English Law governs the access and use of this site and you hereby agree to be bound by the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts. Solid Solutions Management Ltd may vary the Privacy Policy at its sole discretion at any time. 

It is entirely your responsibility to ensure that you check this page each time you access this site to ensure that you are aware of any changes to this privacy policy. 

What personal information does Solid Solutions Management Ltd collect from me?   
Solid Solutions Management Ltd does not collect personal information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. Examples of personal information include name, postal address, and e-mail address. 

Personal information is collected when someone enquires about Solid Solutions Management Ltd's services and in the case of the business being sold, would form part of the sale. 

Data Sharing  
We work with a third party service provider to store data and provide us with information regarding use of the service and traffic on the network, including pages viewed and the actions taken when visiting our website. Our service provider may therefore collect and store certain information about your visits. Our service provider has confirmed that they comply with the requirements of the Data Protection Act.

Copyright   
The design, logos and contents of the website are the property of Solid Solutions Management Ltd. Copying the website is prohibited and its function is to provide information about the services Solid Solutions Management Ltd offers. 

Links   
Solid Solutions Management Ltd's website contains links to other sites that may be of interest to our visitors. This Privacy Policy applies to the SolidSolutions.co.uk website only. 

Use of cookies on our website   
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information about how the website is used. 

We use the following cookies on our website:

  * A number of Google analytics cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports which help us to improve our website. 
  * A temporary session ID cookie is used to make the most efficient use of resources when you are browsing from page to page. The cookie is removed when you leave our website. 
  * A visitor cookie is used to monitor how long a visitor is on our site before they take an action (for example fill in one of our forms to contact us) and also to provide statistics on whether this is a visitor’s first visit to our site. 

These cookies collect information in an anonymous form, we are NOT able to identify individual users from these cookies. 

If you do not wish to allow this use of cookies, you may be able to change the settings on your browser to disable them. There is more information to help you on this link: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

Call Recording  
We may monitor, record, store and use any telephone, email or other communication with you in order to check any instructions given to us, for training purposes, for crime prevention and to improve the quality of our customer service
